<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

  <string-array name="donate_devel_list">
    <!-- item>kencorbin101@gmail.com</item-->
    <item>deweythomas@gmail.com</item>
  </string-array>
  
  <string name="donate_server_url">https://cadpageweb.appspot.com/lookup</string>
  
  <string name="free_release_text"><string>
    This is the free version of Cadpage.  This version will never bother you
    for financial contributions to future Cadpage development.  Customer support
    is minimal, and updates will run 4-6 months behind the standard version.\n
    \n
    If you are new Cadpage user, you should start out using the standard
    Cadpage version.  You can run it for at least 30 days for free during
    which you can take advantage of the very efficient customer support service.\n
    \n
    If you are willing to pay to Cadpage developers to continue supporting 
    Cadpage development, you should use the standard version.\n
    \n
    If you can"'"t afford to the $10 standard payment, you should use the standard
    version and ask for a free subscription.\n
    \n
    If you are adamantly opposed to paying anything on general principle, you
    should still run the standard version for the initial 30 day demo period,
    then switch to this version.
  </string></string>

  <string name="donate_btn_cancel">Cancel</string>
  <string name="donate_btn_done">Done</string>
  <string name="donate_btn_OK">OK</string>
  <string name="donate_btn_yes">Yes</string>
  
  <string name="donate_free_title">This is the free version of Cadpage</string>
  <string name="donate_free_text">
    This is the free version of Cadpage.  It is functionally equivalent to the
    standard version of Cadpage, except that customer support is minimal and
    updates will run 4-6 months behind the standard version. 
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_life_title">Thank you for your support</string>
  <string name="donate_life_text">
    You have earned free, lifetime access to Cadpage. 
    Thank your for you contributions.
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_auth_title">Thank you for your support</string>
  <string name="donate_auth_text">
    You have free access to Cadpage as a member of\n
    %s\n
    Thank you for your support
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_paid_title">Your Cadpage subscription is current</string>
  <string name="donate_paid_text">
    You have a current Cadpage subscription that is good until %s
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_paid_warn_title">Your subscription will expire in %d days</string>
  <string name="donate_paid_warn_text">
    Your current Cadpage subscription will expire on %s.  You can continue to 
    use Cadpage beyond that date as long as you do not install a release
    published after that date.
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_paid_limbo_title">Your Cadpage subscription has expired</string>
  <string name="donate_paid_limbo_text">
    Your current Cadpage subscription expired on %s.  You can continue to 
    use Cadpage as long as you do not install a release published after that date.
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_paid_expire_title">Your Cadpage subscription has expired</string>
  <string name="donate_paid_expire_text">
    Your current Cadpage subscription expired on %s.
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_demo_title">Cadpage demo expires in %d days</string>
  <string name="donate_demo_text">
    You have been using Cadpage for %1$d days, you have %2$d days left before the
    demo expires.
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_demo_expire_title">Your Cadpage demo has expired</string>
  <string name="donate_demo_expire_text">
    You have been using Cadpage for %1$d days.  Your cadpage demo expired %2$d days ago.  
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_android16_title">"Hey, I've already contributed"</string>
  <string name="donate_android16_text">
    Our sincere apologies.  Cadpage tracks you by your Google Market account
    and you are running Android 1.6 which does not gives us the ability to 
    determine your Google Market account.  The good news is that you get a free
    ride as long as you are running Android 1.6.
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_no_user_title">"Hey, I've already contributed"</string>
  <string name="donate_no_user_text">
    Our sincere apologies.  Cadpage tracks you by your Google Market account
    "and you don't seem to have one.  Try logging into the Android Market with"
    your Paypal account and see if that helps.
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_wrong_user_title">"I've made a Paypal payment"</string>
  <string name="donate_wrong_user_text">
    Our sincere apologies.  Cadpage tracks you by your Google Market account
    "which is %s. If this doesn't match the Paypal account you used to pay"
    us, we will need some help figuring out who you are. Just clicking the
    button below will send us an email that will hopefully clear things up.
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_android_title">Purchase through Android Market</string>
  <string name="donate_paypal_title">Purchase through PayPal</string>
  <string name="donate_whats_up_title">What\'s this all about??</string>
  <string name="donate_email_title">Send Email</string>
  
  <string name="donate_android_unsupported_text">
    The Android Market app reports that in-app purchases are not supported.
    You may need to upgrade the Market app to the latest version.  Or you may
    need to give it a valid Google account (Select menu > Accounts in the Market
    app) 
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_android_beta_text">
    For technical reasons, you cannot make Android Market purchases from a beta
    release of Cadpage.  You will have to wait until you install an official
    release of Cadpage from the Android Market.
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_magic_word_title">I have an authorization code</string>
  <string name="donate_magic_word_text">Enter authorization code</string>
  <string name="donate_magic_word_reject">Sorry, that is not a recognized authorization code</string>
  
  <string name="donate_android_problem_title">I can\'t make Android Market payments</string>
  <string name="donate_android_problem_text">
    Bummer, let\'s see what we can do about that.
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_reset_market_title">Recalculate Purchase Status</string>
  
  <string name="donate_sob_story_title">"I can't afford $10"</string>
  <string name="donate_sob_story_text">
    "Tell us why you can't afford a $10 payment.  We're really easy on these.\n\n"
    Is there anything we can do to make Cadpage easier to use?  Do you any
    suggestions on better ways we can finance the considerable costs of maintaining
    Cadpage?
  </string>
  
  <string name="clear_data_title">Reinstall Cadpage</string>
  <string name="clear_data_text">
    This will restart your 30 day demo period.  But it will also erase all app data, 
    including your call history and settings.  Are you sure you want to do this?
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_extra_day_title">Give me another day (%d left)</string>
  
  <string name="donate_exempt_title">Exempt from release checks</string>
  <string name="donate_exempt_text">
    You are exempt from any demo or subscription limits until the next Cadpage
    version update which must be done in the next %d days.
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_cadpage_title">Sponsored by Cadpage</string>
  <string name="donate_cadpage_text">
    You are using a location sponsored by Cadpage.\n 
    Cadpage sponsors the general locations because their performance is 
    unreliable and we do not want to charge users who are waiting until a
    better location can be implemented.
  </string>
  
  <string name="donate_sponsor_title">Sponsored by %s</string>
  <string name="donate_sponsor_text">
    You are using a service sponsored by\n%s\n 
    Support for Cadpage development and maintenance is provided by this
    sponsor.  No further payment is expected from you as long as you
    are using services provided by this sponsor.
  </string>
  
</resources>