<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

  <string name="code_messaging_title">CodeMessaging.net</string>
  <string name="code_messaging_summary">
    Full-featured department messaging platform for routing dispatches
    anywhere and getting alerts out to responders FAST!
  </string>
  <string name="code_messaging_text">
    Send and display your department"'"s dispatches on any device and
    monitor responder status in real-time with Response Check. Users can login
    and send messages within the department as well as manage their own profile
    to route dispatches to any device (phones, pagers, tablets, computers,
    televisions, etc). CodeMessaging.net specializes in bringing control of
    dispatching to the department and responder.
  </string>
  
  <string name="active911_title">Active 911</string>
  <string name="active911_summary">Live response tracking and mapping</string>
  <string name="active911_text">
  Active911 provides a host of services for smartphones, cell phones, and tablets:\n
   - REAL TIME monitoring of response efforts\n
   - LIVE mapping of your entire crew as they respond\n
   - Detailed report generation\n
   - Works on iPhone, Android, Blackberry, and more\n
   - 2 way messaging to provide your crew with supplemental information\n
  </string>
  
  <string name="vendor_notice_title">Cadpage Direct Paging</string>
  
  <string name="vendor_more_info">Tell me more</string>
  <string name="vendor_profile">User Profile</string>
  <string name="vendor_register">Register</string>
  <string name="vendor_unregister">Unregister</string>
  
  <string name="vendor_registered">You are registered for direct paging services</string>
  <string name="vendor_should_register">You should register for direct paging services</string>
  
  <string name="vendor_confirm_unregister">
    This will block this vendor from sending you direct pages.  Are you
    sure that you want to do this?
  </string>
  
  <string name="vendor_connect_msg">Direct paging from %s has been activated</string>
  <string name="vendor_disconnect_msg">Direct paging from %s has been disconnected</string>
  <string name="vendor_reg_failure_msg">
     Google C2DM registration Failed.\n
  </string>
  <string name="vendor_register_err_msg">
    Direct paging from %1$s has been disconnected\n
    Server response: %2$s
  </string>
  <string name="vendor_registration_error">
    Attempt to assign Direct Paging Registration ID has been rejected.  The reported
    error was\n
    %s\n
    Please report this to the Cadpage developers.
  </string>
  <string name="vendor_service_not_available_error">
      The Google servers seem to be busy right now.  Please try again later"
  </string>
  <string name="vendor_account_missing_error">
    A Google account must be registered on this device before you can register
    with a direct paging vendor
  </string>
  <string name="vendor_authentication_failed_error">
    There was an error authenticating the Google Account used by this device.
    Please check that the account and password configured for Google Play Store are valid.  
  </string>
  <string name="vendor_phone_registration_error_error">
    Google says that your phone does not currently support push notifications.  And does not
    give us any hints as just what might be wrong.  More often than not, simply repeating
    the request a few seconds or few days later will work, so try this a couple times before
    giving up and using the Email the Developer support feature to ask for help.  
  </string>
  <string name="vendor_phone_registration_error_hard_error">
    Google says that your phone does not currently support push notifications.  And we do not
    really know why.  Please use the Cadpage Email the Developer setting to ask for additional
    assistance.
  </string>
  <string name="vendor_no_web_viewer_error">
    The system is rejecting requests to view a web page. It would seem that you do not have any kind of web browser app installed.
  </string>
</resources>